{
    "translations": {
        "en": {
            "fa1": "../../../AV/VisFormalLang/NFA/AutomataFiles/NFA2DFA2a.jff",
            "q1": {
                "type": "select",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "if S {a,b,c}, then which of the following is a relation in S",
                "answer": ["(a,c)", "(b,c)", "(c,b)", "(a,a)", "(b,b)", "(c,c)"],
                "choices": ["(a,c)", "(b,c)", "(c,b)", "(a,a)", "(b,b)", "(c,c)"]
            },
            "q2": {
                "type": "select",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "The operator < includes which of the following pairs ordered pairs",
                "answer": ["<1,3>", "<2,23>"],
                "choices": ["<1,3>", "<2,23>", "<3,2>", "<2,2>"]
            },
            "q3":{
                "type": "textBox",
                "question": "What is the infix notation for the pair (4, 5) in the relation <",
                "answer": "4<5"
            },
            "q4": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Is the relation less than or equals reflexive?",
                "answer": ["True"],
                "choices": ["True", "False"]
            },
            "q5": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Is the relation less than or equals irreflexive?",
                "answer": ["False"],
                "choices": ["True", "False"]
            },
            "q6": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Which of the following is a symmetric relation",
                "answer": ["="],
                "choices": ["$<$", "$>$", "="]
            },
            "q7": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Which of the following relation is antisymmetric?",
                "answer": ["$>$"],
                "choices": ["$>$", "=", "$\\leq$"]
            },
            "q8": {
                "type": "select",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Which of the following are transitive relations?",
                "answer": ["$<$", ">", "="],
                "choices": ["$<$", ">", "="]
            },
            "q9": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Which of the following is an equivalence relation?",
                "answer": ["="],
                "choices": ["=", "$<$", "$>$"]
            },
            "q10": {
                "type": "select",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Which of the following are transitive relations?",
                "answer": ["because it is reflective", "because it is symmetric", "because it is transitive"],
                "choices": ["because it is reflective", "because it is symmetric", "because it is transitive"]
            },
            "q11": {
                "type": "textBox",
                "question": "For m = 4, What makes the pair (1, 5) belong to the modulus relation?",
                "answer": "1 mod 4 = 5 mod 4"
            },
            "q12": {
                "type": "select",
                "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
                "question": "Which of the following relations are partial order relations?",
                "answer": ["<", "$\\leq$"],
                "choices": ["<", "$\\leq$", "="]
            }

        }
    }
}
  